Hello everyone, I'm Alice Yamano from Nearly All Joy.
I promised Ayumi-n to go to a bird cafe today.
But we arrived a bit early, so we're waiting for her.
Ayumi-chan has a parakeet called Kee-chan, so I think she's used to birds.
I'm really new to this, so I'm a bit nervous.
Ayumi is here.
Ayumi's here.
Did you wait long?
I just arrived.
I'm glad.
I ordered sushi.
Was it good?
I'm sorry I ate so much.
Ayumi loves sushi.
I'll just accept your feelings.
I came to a cafe with birds today.
I'm here.
How do you like it? Birds.
Birds, but I'm really looking forward to it. It's my first time going to a bird café.
I know, right? You've never bought one before, have you?
I've never bought one.
Then I'll go with you.
Brand, can I see it?
Okay, I'm going in. Let's go!
Sorry to disturb you.
Wow!
So many amazing birds.
Do you want to film this?
Oh, my God.
Thank you very much.
Look at this.
There's so many of them.
Oh, my God.
I'm so happy.
They're lovely.
Good morning. - Good morning.
Good morning.
Takeshi.
She says bye-bye.
Good morning. - Good morning.
Takeshi.
Anger.
Hello.
Can I say bye-bye when you wave?
Do you want to wave together?
Okay.
Bye-bye.
That's great.
Come on, win.
Come on, come on, come on.
I wanted a snack.
I want a snack.
It's twirling.
Good morning.
Did I say good morning to you, too?
That's great, that's great, that's great.
Kobatan.
That's great.
Good morning.
Let's say, "Pay attention"! I'd say, "Stay with me!
"Stay with me! That's great!
She says she gets bothered.
He cries when he's bothered.
Wow, that's great.
Wow!
That's great!
That's amazing.
You're getting excited, Bamboo-chan.
I sometimes bite my customers, especially men, because I'm an old man.
She sometimes bites her customers, especially men.
Is that so?
I'm 19.
I'll live about 60 years.
I'm like a JK.
So men tend to give me a bit of a hard time.
I see.
We don't get bitten, do we?
He likes to oyster-quick through his gauge.
What do you try to do with the oysters?
Does he bite your hand like a normal person?
Is that okay?
He doesn't bite the oysters.
From me?
Oyster bite.
Don't touch my eyes.
Oh, no, it's a beautiful white one.
It's so fluffy!
That's great!
You know, Kee-chan...
I know that parakeet Kee-chan, he won't let me touch him at all.
Is that so?
He bites me all the time, so I thought he might bite me.
You're amazing, Bamboo.
He doesn't bite at all.
You've got a great voice.
Bamboo, I'm happy to be bit.
Tick-tock!
Here, you're an owl.
Alice, you're an owl.
I thought you said you missed me.
I love you so much.
I'm so happy.
I don't know. I mean, I've never...
I never said I wanted to make eye contact.
I'd like to make eye contact.
I think he's looking at you. So is Alice.
It was so cute, like she was winking at him, like she was trying to make eye contact.
It's kind of cute, like she's winking at you.
He's with Alice.
I bet she's winking at you so much.
She's so cute.
Thank you.
He'll eat it.
Wow.
Look at this.
Please give me some food and meat.
I'll bring it up to you and see if you'll eat it, and bring it to your mouth.
Eat it! It ate it! Gone in a second?
Gone?
He ate it in one gulp.
He ate it all up.
He's so cute.
So cute.
Hey, maybe the girl next door will go, too.
The girl next door is going, too.
Cute.
Cute little mouth.
He's got such beautiful eyes.
He ate it!
Beautiful eyes. Amazing orange.
I'd like to take them up a bit in order.
It's so clear.
It's kind of stuck.
He ate it.
Oh, my God.
You're raising it so high.
He's so cute.
It's so cute.
So cute. So cute.
Looks like he's eating well.
So cute.
It jumped up.
I'll give you the last one then.
Here you go.
It's all gone.
They're all gone.
Okay, I'll show you what's inside.
4 I'm in there, and... well... it looks like we could eat it, too.
There's a cup of corn, some nuts and vegetables, which we'll give to the birds now.
He's been very appealing since a while ago.
I wonder if he'll eat it.
Alice, you want to try it?
Quick.
He's dying for it.
Carrots?
Carrots. - They're cute, they're cute, they're cute, they're cute, they're cute, they're cute, they're cute, they're cute, they're cute, they're nuts, nuts.
Nuts are amazing.
I showed them to you right away.
He's going to go.
Oh, he's here!
He's so cute!
Oh, my God.
Nuts are dancing...
Oh, my God, they're dropping me!
Do you think he'll go for it?
I've given up! I've been dropped!
Good morning! Good morning!
You want to go nuts?
I'm going!
Good morning!
Yes, shall we go?
I've changed. Poncho?
Poncho. Does it suit you?
You look really cute, Alice.
Ayumi is cute too.
I'm healed.
Then I'd like to go inside now.
Let's go!
That's great. A bit like this.
It's that thing, isn't it?
It's like going natural.
To Amazon.
Amazon is amazing.
It's like an amazing attraction inside.
It's exotic.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's gonna sound amazing.
I wonder if it pushes.
Is it hard? Can I...
This way?
Oh, hello. Is it hard? This way? Whoa!
Hello!
Oh, no!
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God, you have such beautiful eyes.
You have such beautiful eyes.
Good morning, good morning.
Who's there? Who's there? Who's who?
He's got a bit of a face.
Who's who?
Oh, my God.
Who's that?
Who's that? He's here again, and he's talking right here.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Sorry.
I'm here, me.
You're eating the wrong food.
I'll do my best. Good luck.
I'm eating.
Mm-hm.
All right. All right.
Wow! That's great!
It's got so much oomph!
Yeah!
Oh, my God, she's amazing.
Let's go around.
Oh, my God!
She's got a lot of momentum.
Let's go around.
Oh, my gosh.
Amazing.
There's a lot of them here, too.
They're like toys.
There's one here.
Okinawan boars.
Is it?
So cute.
Oh, here it comes!
Cute.
Superhero outfit.
You did your best.
Shall we ride with Ayumi?
She's cute.
So cute.
She's so sweet. She's totally in love with you.
Human clothes.
Ayumi's.
And Alice, too. That girl's become my partner.
Aaah!
Oh, oh, oh!
That's a great baby hugger.
She's holding a baby.
Oh, he's so cute.
I'm so happy for this baby.
It's like she's holding a baby.
That's so cute.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Cute little thing, it stings.
I'm so happy to see you, I feel like I'm a slave.
Alice was really popular.
Ayumi's head was full of them.
Her shoulders were so cute... it was so relaxing.
Next we'll look at the merchandise.
If I find something good I'll buy it for Kiki as a souvenir.
Let's find some.
Then let's find some.
Okay.
Cute!
It's cute.
What's this?
It's a stuffed animal.
About the size of Kii?
Yes, about Kitty's size.
Just like this.
It's so cute!
I kind of want to meet Kii-chan.
Cute straw hat.
What do you think? What size do you think, Kii?
It's perfect.
I think it'll fit her perfectly, but she might be scared.
Scared?
Yes, Kii, I've bought her lots of these colours and lots of these.
But she got scared of them all and couldn't go near them anymore.
I don't know, maybe something white or something.
I think she might not be scared if it's not a flashy colour, or if it's not too big.
I'm not sure about the colour of the Osume for small parrots, though...
Colour
Kee-chan...
Is there one you'd like to buy, Alice?
Alice, did you ever think about buying one of these?
I didn't buy any, I just thought they'd be cute as heck or stuffed animals.
Today it's a parakeet.
That's too funny.
Have you become interested in parakeets and birds today?
I'm so interested in them, I want one.
I want to buy one? I want to buy one? But, Kii, I want to see you again.
See you again? See you next time. I want you to show me next time.
Someday, I want to see you again, Kii.
But Alice was so unafraid of all the big birds...
I'm sure Kin-chan can handle it. She's much more gentle.
She's cute. She's cute.
Today we visited a cafe with birds.
If you liked it, please click the Good button and subscribe to our channel.
That's me, Ayaris Yamanashi and Nayumi Ichigaya. Bye bye, watch!